What is Bitregion...
and how can you get a donation up to 30,000 BTC...
by just contributing only 0.15 BTC to the community?
before that, how about we see how donation can help to collect hugh amount of money within a short period of time.
Lets say if you urgently need financial help and there are 30,000 over the internet that feel sympathy with your emergency situation...
If everyone contribute 1 BTC each, the donation fund collected is about 30,000 BTC.
Actually, it is really simple.
It's just that, you are not in the position that this 30,000 people feels sympathy with your situation...
And not to mention how to collect 1 BTC from each of them without any valid reason.
Another way that sounds interesting is playing 'Mutual Fund'.
Have you heard about 'Mutual Fund' scheme before this?